Roxane Connick Carlisle collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 2: Sound recordings
  - Subseries 3: Listen to the world (radio broadcasts), This radio series ran from about 1971-1973, and broadcast on CHEX-FM, Peterborough, Ontario. The shows were produced, written, and narrated by Roxane Connick Carlisle.
    - Listen to the World - China, July 11, 1971, 1 sound tape reel (60 min. 15 sec.): analog, 3 3/4 ips, 1 track; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2012/008: SR126)
      See the note for SR119. Broadcast date: July 11, 1971. SR126 and SR160 may be a master tape and a copy of the same recording.
    - Listen to the World - China, July 11, 1971, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips, 1 track; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2012/008: SR160)
      See the note for SR126.
    - Listen to the World - Arabic musical tradition in North Africa: Arabic traditional: Tunisia, Algeria, Libya, Chad, Sudan, July 16, 1971, 1 sound tape reel (62 min.): analog, 3 3/4 ips, 1 track; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2012/008: SR127)
      See the note for SR119. SR127 and SR156 may be a master tape and a copy of the same recording.
    - Listen to the World - Arabic musical tradition in North Africa: Arabic traditional: Tunisia, Algeria, Libya, Chad, Sudan, July 16, 1971, 1 sound tape reel (62 min.): analog, 3 3/4 ips, 1 track; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2012/008: SR156)
      See the notes for SR119 and SR127.
    - Listen to the World - the music of Burundi, July 23, 1971, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips, 1 track; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2012/008: SR128)
      See the note for SR119. SR128 may be a master tape and SR165 a copy of the same recording.
    - Listen to the World - the music of Burundi, July 23, 1971, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips, 1 track; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2012/008: SR165)
      See the note for SR128.
    - Listen to the World - Southeast Africa, August 1971, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips, 1 track; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2012/008: SR129)
      See the note for SR119. Broadcast date: August 1971.
    - Listen to the World - Southeast Africa, August 1971, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips, 1 track; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2012/008: SR155)
      See the note for SR119. Broadcast date: August 1971. Possibly a copy of SR129.
    - Listen to the World - the music of the Philippines and Sulu Sea Islands, September 19, 1971, 1 sound tape reel (59 min. 30 sec.): analog, 3 3/4 ips, 1 track; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2012/008: SR130)
      See the note for SR119. Recorded September 19, 1971. SR130 and SR167 may be a master tape and a copy of the same recording.
    - Listen to the World - Philippines, 1 sound tape reel: analog; analog, 3 3/4 ips, 1 track; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2012/008: SR167)
      See the note for SR130.
    - Listen to the World - the music of Japan, October 15 and 17, 1971, 1 sound tape reel (60 min.): analog, 3 3/4 ips, 1 track; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2012/008: SR131)
      See the note for SR119. Recorded October 15, 1971. Broadcast date: October 17, 1971. SR131 and SR163 may be a master tape and a copy of the same recording.
    - Listen to the World - the music of Japan, October 15 and 17, 1971, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2012/008: SR163)
      See the note for SR131.
    - Listen to the World - Indians of Mexico, October 29 and 31, 1971, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips, 1 track; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2012/008: SR132)
      See the note for SR119. Recorded October 29, 1971. Broadcast date: October 31, 1971. SR132 and SR162 may be a master tape and a copy of the same recording.
    - Listen to the World - Indians of Mexico, October 29 and 31, 1971, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips, 1 track; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2012/008: SR162)
      See the note for SR132.
    - Listen to the World - North American Indian, November 14, 1971, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips, 1 track; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2012/008: SR133)
      See the note for SR119. Broadcast date: November 14, 1971. SR133 and SR166 may be a master tape and a copy of the same recording.
    - Listen to the World - North American Indian, November 14, 1971, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips, 1 track; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2012/008: SR166)
      See the note for SR133.
    - Listen to the World - Indonesia, November 25 and 28, 1971, 1 sound tape reel (61 min.): analog, 3 3/4 ips, 1 track; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2012/008: SR134)
      See the note for SR119. Recorded November 25, 1971. Broadcast date: November 28, 1971. Celebes - Sudanese - Balinese - Javanese.
    - Listen to the World - Indonesia (copy), November 25 and 28, 1971, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2012/008: SR135)
      See the notes for SR134.
    - Listen to the World - India, part 1: North India, circa 1971-1973, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2012/008: SR136)
    - Listen to the World - India, part 1: North India (copy), circa 1971-1973, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2012/008: SR138)
      See the note for SR136.
    - Listen to the World - India, part 2: South India, circa 1971-1973, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips, 1 track; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2012/008: SR137)
    - Listen to the World - India, part 2: South India (copy), circa 1971-1973, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2012/008: SR139)
    - Listen to the World - Ethiopia, circa 1971-1973, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips, 1 track; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2012/008: SR141)
      SR141 and SR161 may be a master tape and a copy of the same recording.
    - Listen to the World - Ethiopia, circa 1971-1973, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips, 1 track; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2012/008: SR161)
      See the note for SR141.
    - Listen to the World - Central Africa: music of the great forests, circa 1971-1973, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips, 1 track; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2012/008: SR142)
    - Listen to the World - Central Africa: music of the great forests (copy), circa 1971-1973, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2012/008: SR140)
      See the note for SR142.
    - Listen to the World - Brazil, circa 1971-1973, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips, 1 track; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2012/008: SR143)
      SR143 and SR158 may be a master tape and a copy of the same recording.
    - Listen to the World - Brazil, circa 1971-1973, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips, 1 track; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2012/008: SR158)
      See the note for SR143.
  - Subseries 4: Abdel Karim El Kably
    - el Kably, ud, home, April 2, 1963, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, 1 track; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2012/008: SR003)
      Recorded at the home of el Kably. The ud he plays is a five-string instrument with sympathetic strings.
    - el Kably, Sudan Culture Center, August 3, 1963, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2012/008: SR062)
      First third of tape there are echo and crowd noises, and el Kably's voice is indistinct.
    - el Kably, July 13, 1963, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, 1 track; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2012/008: SR054)
      Recorded at the home of el Kably, in Khartoum North (El Danagra Shamal).
    - el Kably, July 13, 1963, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, 1 track; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2012/008: SR055)
      Recorded at the home of Abdel Karim el Kably, in Khartoum North.
    - el Kably, four songs, ud and drums, July 20, 1963, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2012/008: SR056)
      Recorded in the evening, in Omdurman. In a note accompanying the recording, written to a Mrs. Rodgers, El Kabli spells his surname with an "i."
    - el Kably interview, three songs, September 5, 1963, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips, 1 track; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2012/008: SR068)
      Interview with Abdel Karim el Kably, at the home of Mrs. Robert Jackson, in Mogren, Khartoum. Three Sudanese songs sung by el Kably. Conversation with Roxane McCollester, later with Carol Jackson.
    - Abdel Karim el Kably I, 1 sound tape reel (27 min. 44 sec.): analog, 7 1/2 ips, 1 track, mono; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2012/008: SR175)
      Sampler; six songs. First-generation copy.
    - Abdel Karim el Kably II, 1 sound tape reel (25 min. 14 sec.): analog, 7 1/2 ips, 1 track, mono; 7 in. (Item id AFC 2012/008: SR176)
      Sampler; five songs. First-generation copy.
    - Sudan: the music and songs of Abdel Karim el Kably, August 1963, 1 sound disc (vinyl): analog, 33 1/3 rpm. (Item id AFC 2012/008: SR191)
      See box-folder 1/12. 3 pages of handwritten notes by Abdel Karim el Kably accompanied SR191. This broad overview about music in Sudan was written for Carlisle at el Kably's home in Khartoum North in August 1963.
- Series 3: Photographs, Due to the small space in which to write on the slide mats, some of the information is unclear or difficult to understand. Carlisle's spelling of proper names of locations or ethnic groups reflect contemporary spelling. In these cases, the first instance is revised to reflect current usage, and all instances after that silently revised.
  - Subseries 1: Amin family and friends: private activities at home in Omdurman
    - Col. Osman Amin on terrace of his home in Omdurman, March 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0001 (Box 6)
    - Men's entrance of Amin Compound, Omdurman, March 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0002 (Box 6)
    - Col. Osman Amin in car approaching home in Omdurman, March 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0003 (Box 6)
    - Col. Osman Amin's servant opening men's entrance to Amin compound, Omdurman, March 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0004 (Box 6)
    - Col. Osman Amin entering his house in Omdurman, March 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0005 (Box 6)
    - Col. Osman Amin entering his house in Omdurman, March 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0006 (Box 6)
    - Col. Osman Amin on his reception porch of home in Omdurman, March 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0007 (Box 6)
    - Col. Osman Amin at Omdurman home, March 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0008 (Box 6)
    - Col. Osman Amin's car in Omdurman home courtyard, March 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0009 (Box 6)
    - Col. Osman Amin's car in court in Omdurman, March 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0010 (Box 6)
    - Col. Osman Amin ordering lunch from Yassein in Omdurman home, March 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0011 (Box 6)
    - Abu Roof Strut / Omdurman from Col. Amin's car, March 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0012 (Box 6)
    - Col. Osman Amin on terrace of Omdurman home, March 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0013 (Box 6)
    - Atoma Amin / F52, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0014 (Box 6)
    - Atoma Amin / F52, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0015 (Box 6)
    - Affaf Hassan and Atoma Amin, schoolmaster, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0016 (Box 6)
    - Affaf Hassan and Atoma Amin, schoolmaster; Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0017 (Box 6)
    - Hassan and Atoma Amin, Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0018 (Box 6)
    - Hassan, Atoma and schoolmaster, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0019 (Box 6)
    - Affaf Amin shying away, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0020 (Box 6)
    - Col. Amin's car, September 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0021 (Box 6)
      The date is taken from the lab stamp on the slide mount.
    - Roxane before Amin compound / F50 / Omdurman, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0022 (Box 6)
    - Street near Amin compound, September 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0023 (Box 6)
    - Col. Amin's servant Yassein at women's gate to compound; at left, water jug for travellers to use, September 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0024 (Box 6)
    - Men's entrance to Amin compound, September 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0025 (Box 6)
    - Men's entrance to Amin compound, September 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0026 (Box 6)
    - Col. Amin's servant pressing a uniform, September 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0027 (Box 6)
    - Amin terrace (#38), June 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0028 (Box 6)
    - Roxane and Bakhita along Nile / F50, August 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0029 (Box 6)
    - Roxane and Bakhita in front of Amin compound / F50, circa March-September 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0030 (Box 6)
    - Bakhita Amin / F51, July 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0031 (Box 6)
    - Sharaf on his bicycle, Amin compound / Omdurman, circa March-September 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0032 (Box 6)
    - Cooking house - Amin compound / Omdurman, circa March-September 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0033 (Box 6)
    - Bakhita and morning oranges / our beds in her courtyard - Omdurman / F32, circa March-September 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0034 (Box 6)
    - Bakhita, Amin compound / Omdurman / F32, circa March-September 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0035 (Box 6)
    - Amin servant, children near cooking house of Amin compound / Omdurman / F32, circa March-September 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0036 (Box 6)
    - Cooking house and children of Amin compound in Omdurman / F32, circa March-September 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0037 (Box 6)
    - Sayeeda Haram Amin resting - Amin house / Omdurman / F32, circa March-September 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0038 (Box 6)
    - Amin cousin in passageway to Bakhita's room / Amin compound / Omdurman / F32, circa March-September 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0039 (Box 6)
    - Amin cousin in passageway to Bakhita's room / Amin compound / Omdurman / F32, circa March-September 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0040 (Box 6)
    - Servant reassuring Idriss, two Mustafa girls / Amin compound / Omdurman / F32, circa March-September 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0041 (Box 6)
    - Sharaf and sleeping Hassan - Amin house / Omdurman / F32, circa March-September 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0042 (Box 6)
    - Sharaf looking into cooking house / Amin compound / Omdurman / F32, circa March-September 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0043 (Box 6)
    - Hassan Amin, the writer and poet / Omdurman / F32, circa March-September 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0044 (Box 6)
    - Hassan Amin / Omdurman, circa March-September 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0045 (Box 6)
    - Bakhita and Haram Amin / Omdurman, circa March-September 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0046 (Box 6)
    - Haram Amin (red shawl) on way to visit her neighbor Hassuna / Omdurman, circa March-September 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0047 (Box 6)
    - Hassan teasing Fatna during meal preparation / Amin compound / Omdurman, circa March-September 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0048 (Box 6)
    - Bakhita and Hassam Amin / Omdurman, circa March-September 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0049 (Box 6)
    - Amin cousin, son, friend / Amin compound / Omdurman, circa March-September 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0050 (Box 6)
    - Fatna, Bakhita and Hassan preparing meal / Amin compound / Omdurman, circa March-September 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0051 (Box 6)
    - Bakhita and Hayat Tayeb / F36 / el Hassanim, circa March-September 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0052 (Box 6)
    - Bakhita Amin in her garden / Omdurman, circa March-September 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0053 (Box 6)
    - Bakhita Amin in her garden / Omdurman, circa March-September 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0054 (Box 6)
    - Bakhita Amin on men's terrace / Amin compound / Omdurman, circa March-September 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0055 (Box 6)
    - Bakhita Amin on men's terrace / Amin compound / Omdurman, circa March-September 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0056 (Box 6)
    - Son of one of Bakhita Amin's friends / Omdurman, circa March-September 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0057 (Box 6)
    - Bakhita and three friends in Onduman Street, circa March-September 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0058 (Box 6)
    - Interior of Hassuna's (yellow shawl) sleeping porch, Omdurman, circa March-September 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0059 (Box 6)
    - Hassuna (yellow shawl) and friend in her sleeping porch, Omdurman, circa March-September 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0060 (Box 6)
    - Sharafnin [?] Idriss' bed / Amin compound / Omdurman, circa March-September 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0061 (Box 6)
    - Hassan Amin / Omdurman, circa March-September 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0062 (Box 6)
    - Hassan Amin / Omdurman, circa March-September 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0063 (Box 6)
    - Hassan Amin / Omdurman, circa March-September 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0064 (Box 6)
    - Hassan Amin with his first book / Omdurman, circa March-September 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0065 (Box 6)
    - Hassan Amin with his first book / Omdurman, circa March-September 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0066 (Box 6)
    - Bakhita and cousin having tea at Amin compound - Omdurman, circa March-September 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0067 (Box 6)
    - Amin cousin / Omdurman, circa March-September 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0068 (Box 6)
    - Hassuna and friend in Amin compound / Omdurman, circa March-September 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0069 (Box 6)
    - Hassuna and friend in Amin compound / Omdurman, circa March-September 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0070 (Box 6)
    - Bakhita Amin having hair braided - Omdurman, circa March-September 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0071 (Box 6)
    - Bakhita having hair braided - Omdurman, circa March-September 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0072 (Box 6)
    - Idriss and two cousins in Amin compound / Omdurman, circa March-September 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0073 (Box 6)
    - Bakhita having hair braided - Omdurman, circa March-September 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0074 (Box 6)
  - Subseries 2: Awad al Karim, slide carousel 1 - family activities at home / Hayat and Abdulmagid's wedding / Abdulmagid and relatives / photos of preparations, the djertig, and the wedding parties (Omdurman, Sudan Republic)
    - Flowers in Awad el Karim compound, Omdurman, 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0075 (Box 6)
    - Amina and Baset with sisters and cousins - Awad el Karim, 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0076 (Box 6)
    - Amina and Baset with sisters and cousins - Awad el Karim, 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0077 (Box 6)
    - Abdel Baset Awad el Karim with ud / Omdurman, 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0078 (Box 6)
    - Abdel Baset Awad el Karim with ud / Omdurman, 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0079 (Box 6)
    - Abdel Baset and Seig / Mohammed before Khalifa's home / F2, 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0080 (Box 6)
    - Hayat's mother, Roxane with ud and sisters and cousins / Awad el Karim compound / Omdurman, 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0081 (Box 6)
    - Amina / Awad el Karim, 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0082 (Box 6)
    - Hayat's mother and Malchita in Awad el Karim compound / Omdurman, 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0083 (Box 6)
    - Hayat's mother on her way to kitchen to offer guests refreshment / Omdurman, 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0084 (Box 6)
    - Hayat's grandmother in Awad compound / Omdurman, 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0085 (Box 6)
    - Hayat's grandmother, 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0086 (Box 6)
    - Old fighting swords of the Awad el Karim family / Omdurman, May 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0087 (Box 6)
    - Hayat Awad el Karim with old sword and dagger / Omdurman, May 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0088 (Box 6)
    - Hayat Awad el Karim and fighting sword / Omdurman, 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0089 (Box 6)
    - Mahdi revolt sword type from Awad el Karim / Omdurman, 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0090 (Box 6)
    - Hayat, Samira, cousins of Awad el Karim / Omdurman, May 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0091 (Box 6)
    - Hayat Awad, sister and cousins / Omdurman, May 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0092 (Box 6)
    - Hayat / F47, 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0093 (Box 6)
    - Hayat and Roxane / F47, 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0094 (Box 6)
    - Hayat Awad, Hayat and Mahaesin (cousins) / F47, 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0095 (Box 6)
    - Hayat's mother and sister, 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0096 (Box 6)
    - Hayat, Amal, Amina in Awad el Karim compound / Omdurman, 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0097 (Box 6)
    - Hayat, aunt and sister, 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0098 (Box 6)
    - Hayat, aunt and sister, 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0099 (Box 6)
    - Hayat reading, 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0100 (Box 6)
    - Hayat reading, 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0101 (Box 6)
    - Hayat Awad el Karim / Omdurman, May 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0102 (Box 6)
    - Hayat Awad el Karim / Omdurman, May 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0103 (Box 6)
    - Hayat, Amal, Mahmoud Hayat Awad el Karim / Omdurman, May 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0104 (Box 6)
    - Hayat Awad el Karim on her prayer mat / Omdurman, May 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0105 (Box 6)
    - Naima and Hayat's sister before Hayat's wedding, 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome II; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0106 (Box 6)
    - Naim Awad el Karim / Omdurman, May 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0107 (Box 6)
    - Naim Awad el Karim / Omdurman, May 1963, 1 slide: color, Kodachrome; 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH0108 (Box 6)